This video volume can find niches on Chrome Webster Marketplace.
As you can see, you have Freeman categories, productivity, lifestyle and make from yours,
which consists of accessibility, functionality in new high and privacy and security.
We see some you might like, it will be tailored to your needs,
so for the place for your tags, all is safe, especially for multiple places,
there's more money cut to the GPT, so your assistant in chat GPT here.
There's the conquer the clutter, so extension for spring cleaning, your browser,
bookmarks quick search, trigger for a demo, and there is the connectable disable Chrome extension,
extensity.
Okay, that's a great thing, obviously you can open a new eco-gita mode if you don't want to.
Use our next extension, this is control of your tab session, buddy, you tab redirecting,
there are some subcategories that help with AI assistance.
We have an outdoor, so you have power to have forecasting, it will be a great combination,
there are some even retro games that you can play directly, straight from the web browser.
So even if I have this one, you use some users, I can add it to Chrome,
I'll add this to our extension, and we show you how it actually looks like.
So we can have an extension, this is the game, and obviously from here, what I can do,
I can speed it up, open it up here, straight and press start, select the level,
and as you can see, I'm able to do it, which is great, and obviously we can go through
the level, another stuff, and we control two characters in order to move, so great.
And this is how it works, like if it decreases, as well, if you close a regular E2 reset,
so this is how it works.
And as well, if you come back, there are obviously other retro games, so if you're interested
in creating the game and nesting, the Chrome extension, as you can see, there are some.
You see even the number of reviews and ratings, so how is this a iterative thing, all right.
It's rather to show your skills, not exactly to monetize it, but it is what it is.
So from now, I will go to the productivity.
So first category is communication, and here we can just the highest rated at most relevant.
So highest rated, obviously, it will not show the most popular, but the one with the best
average score, and as you can see, for most relevant, we see a note tiger.
You can see actually how it's placed from order to 100,000, it's for taking notes.
This is the screen pole.
It's a very interesting tool that you can record the screen, and then screenshot and
all this stuff across that one.
There is even access to Webter.
It's for Germany email.
There is a sign several in encryption, Gauss-Rite, social DPT, AI, MIDI, and notes.
So there are many possibilities to create an extension through my AI for Chrome.
There are some developer tools.
Go for podcasts that I'll show you when you can do a screenshot of entire page, and
there's a PDF or no more image.
There is a supercharge.
We have a site checker, omnibook, this UI version, user agent, switcher, the gripper, color
tab.
So there are some extensions that actually allow you to see what is inside.
Obviously, you can use the load mode, see more of them, take boomerang, caress, and this
is more like taking a oriented, and you can even measure pixels, that's right.
So you have a designer tools.
If you like your designer and some of the tools that are not here, obviously you can
add it under developer tools.
There is a location, so a presentation for Chrome is good, actually, it's a known stuff
from e-readers, like Kindle, and the specified that you can use, as well, another CD.
And obviously they offer some of the premium versions.
So you can monetize it, there's a reversal translation, I really like that.
Sorry, it's because it's not just translating, it just checks if it was used in Android
calls or books, so you know that the current sentence is correct.
This is for tools, so as you can see, for the tools you will see, all of the stuff related
to Google Impad, we have a JPG.
This is very light screenshot tool, I know it, you can basically create all of the tools,
keywords, you ever suggest, a hunter for finding emails, as well as a pay version, so you
can monetize it easily, and there are the QR code generators and scratch.
This is another automating work with VAi.
Improve for YouTube, you have a tiny eye, there is no JPT, a video player, Santa
Harsew and Finding Nemos, Finding Nemos are very popular extensions, as well as Santa
Hire is just the same as Hunter for Finding Nemos, so it's a great niche.
Work flow and planning, so from here as you can see, you can specify and save some stuff.
This is like Go Keep Chrome but you can save the Pinterest, you can have, you are not web
people, so if you have a service, it's great to have an extension to add some additional
functionality, so people will be able to know your extension and use of your programs.
You obviously add an additional layer of possibilities to use some of the functionalities
from your success service.
This is our design, so in our design, as you can see, it's mostly related to adjusting
the look of your Chrome, but as well, you can image the node, you have other inbuilt
in the Chrome extension, the back ones for Chrome, the image for the day, so we show in
the verpy link at the top page, there's a photo editor, homepage, run store, it's hard
to monetize, but still there are some possibilities, entertainment, so watch together, actually,
it's very popular extensions, you can watch some videos to go with other people, it's
equalizer or crumbs, with the cursor, it takes customizes sounds, the best thing is just
try to look for a niche that you found in other platforms, but it's not on Chrome and
Chrome, obviously it's a home for more than a billion people, so you'll be able to actually
have access to the many people for using Chrome extension, to crunch all some ultra-wide streaming,
and for special devices, it can be always loose, I shall previously reach your game, whether
it's the other box really bound, picks up box jumping menus, people love box jumping
menu, pick so games, if you have here, all you can create menu free games, and then after
that that's some payload, some might be from people might actually use it, this is everything
metric automatic you need to convert, it's a nice, obviously if you are from US and try
to convert quickly, you'll be able to do it, this is for currency, so because you can see
convert is a popular, this is chatbot's place, it'll be able to use all of the items, straight
from your web browser, this is just for fun, this is actually for production, so you see
dislikes on YouTube, I'm using it as well, this is a shimingy browser extension, so we can
play, they're like a clicker, I will games, it can be played straight from the web browser,
the frontest faces, this is the Twitch, and stuff, this is the new some web server, fake
use the bunker from, we verify that I'm using as well, and RSS feed reader, for feed
readers it's very great niche, but you have to own your own server, but as you can see
from the top eight, there are free readers in the reader, RSS feed reader and feed lead, notifier,
I try it free of them, it's a great niche to cause, and in the monetize, especially for
custom, it will be able to build your own system for RSS feed, you can easily offer it
for free, for example for some of the custom stuff, for some of the usage, and I love
for example, people to make a premium thing, so I have a RSS feed reader now, so some
of it's actually paid, some of it's free, but you will be able to know what actually
free can you do it, so this is the free, I have possibility to have 200, but I can upgrade,
and Android allows us these tools, and you can create something like that, and maybe lower
down the price, maybe add something in the another plan, and the best thing is just to
try another, and see the prices, so we can go to maybe try this one, so in a reader and
feed the reader, so in a reader, okay, let me try it, this is the feed lead, notifier,
so you can actually use it, oh this is the Chrome extension, so this is for free, and so
you will be able actually to set it down for yourself, go Chrome extension, for the
news, and yeah, we can even build a version, and this is the inner reader, this 100% is
just paid extension, so if you go to inner reader, we'll be able to see prices, I will
go get it, let me see the pricing, and now we have some initial stuff, this is 667, for
create monitoring, and for feed lead, and not feed lead, but erases feeder, if I go there for feeder,
come, I'll go get it, we are able to compare no pricing, so you see, the inner reader is
more cheap, and we see possibilities and as well, so it's popular, but we use the erases,
so we'll be able to do it, this is go about wever, stickers, by users, this is the tick thought
with your wallet, some of the other extending tools that you can use, the New York Times,
this is her own alarm, the weather now, this is the live versus bookmarks, another bookmarks
that you can synchronize, it's good to actually have a synchronization, this is the COVID
stats, I don't think it's very popular now, so let's see, let's not do it, this is
the field brush, what the popular, fortunately sometimes you just go with the most relevant,
obviously you can use the highest rated and filter out by future editors and see, but here
we'll be able to select extensions that have, for example, positive, but only 6 reviews,
so still I would suggest you to basically load more and see how to make it just basically
more detailed flow, to make it more detailed data, this was shopping, keep eyes were popular
obviously, for Amazon tracking, for automatic coupon, they come out as a cash box service
like the shops, the coupon boards, alley tools, for shopping, I'd rather shopping assistants
the pie shopping, we have a baby list pattern, I'll help many of these tools are actually
cash box tools, and finding coupons, all just tools that exist, possibly to do the most
of them from Ali, and it's probably our safe place, Ali price tracker, I search by image,
Ali, per casing assistant, this is fairly bad, but this is Ali price, so the Ali tools
are the most popular, and you have to basically watch, but there is a coupon, keep eyes for
Amazon price tracker, and this is basically the only tool that have some sort of the monopoly,
and if you'll be able to develop your own and set up your own prices, you'll be able
to do it, I would just manage the extension and don't know that, so this is the extension,
okay, I would just press right and I remove from Chrome, and then I would go to keep on,
and when I have a keep on, this converts, it goes directly to your platform, and now you'll
be able to see all of the DS and tracking, so you can see I'm looking for watches, and
this is the German watches, and on the left I have track ranges, and keep that in mind,
this data is available here, but there is as well as a bit to buy a subscription, so from
here you can get access to subscription, and you'll be able to see sales, buying rank history,
and buy book statistics, eBay price history, and all this stuff, it's 20 euro per month,
so you can set it up for 1482, and be able to actually do, push your own product, social
networking, so obviously if you have some interesting idea for extending or editing some stuff
from social media, how is it just you to do so, the story server is one of the favorite
one, because you can easily save stories from Facebook, Instagram, and WhatsApp, technical
to your PC with the full quality, as you can see, it's very extension, so you will not
be able to monetize it, and there are some other even alternatives, but this one is the
most popular, social blade stats, so if you would like to have extension that gives insight
above statistics in some of the platforms, you will be able to do it, even new extension
that returns all Twitter looks, so you can even try to bring the old look of Twitter, this
is for traveling, obviously for traveling, you still will be finding some extension, even
that can be monetized, like cheap flight finders or some same finders, some travel arrows,
some hotels, other travel monkey, hunter ninja, particularly the guest book extension,
and casual and new book directly with a hotel, some cutbacks and other platforms, it's not
popular, but still you will be able to actually find something, and this is for why being
here, you do the Pro Fixer, undistracted, current up, yeah, if you're a Muslim, and there
is like a postural minder, so it's tip up straight, if you remind you actually about it,
you'll be able to set some of the notification and play with it, as soon as you do create
a few three apps, and try to redirect them directly to the extensions that has some paid
function of, it's like we see here, and yeah, this is the main crumbs yours, it will
allow us to enhance it, as we can see the Roblox is popular here, the copy fish is OCR
platform, Alapla scappy protection, we have some stuff that allow us to, this is the
Alao copying some of the website, do not allow us to copy some of the stuff, and this
extension prevents it, I really recommend that screen shader, so it's Chrome, some of
the orange color, it's popular that you have on your phone, so you can obviously use it
as an extension, too, this is the creator, so it's which any web page is to the dark
mode, to the care of your eyes, even if it doesn't have this as dark corridor as well,
this is available here, some Synology extension, and this is the functionality in UI, so
another stuff that you'll be able to adjust it, so as you can see, this is an ultra wide,
there is a sponsor block for you to tap session manager, we see a lot of the extensions
here, which is great, except for cookies, clean your tap, and customize Roblox is very
popular as well with that category, and this is privacy, it's only if you're a specialist
or have a service like VPN, maybe some extension that will prevent some of the leaking of
your professional data or hardening of your web browser, you should be able to add it
as an extension, as an additional tool, or maybe some directly stuff, this is a much
private environment, they have their own service, but you can see there is no passport
manager, pocket universe, VPN type, decentralized, you'll be able to find many extra
extensions that you can use, especially when it comes to safety, and I highly suggest you
to try them out and see whatever it fits you well, these are mostly addition to the main
service that you are by, but still, it's possible to create a single standard extension
and monetize it, so as you can see there are many categories, just to find one, the
most extensions that you are mostly interested, play them out, and then basically type
that extension into GURAC, or maybe CHA-GPT, or another other studio, what functionality
are needed to that service, and basically try to extract as many information from that
app, by using LLM, and then to put that LLM information into cursor or any other AI tool
that will help you to review that tool by using information that we were given by LLM.